Guide to the Group Material Archive 1976-2009 (bulk 1979-1996) MSS.215
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Project Files, 204535
  - Subseries B: Projects exhibited in public spaces and other venues, 1981-1990; 210170
    - "Democracy" (Brochures and Ads for Book), 1988-1990; 204731 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - "Democracy" (Notes, Drafts, Statements for Book), 1988-1990; 204732 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Other Drafts for Book 1, 1988-1990; 204733 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Other Drafts for Book 2, 1988-1990; 204734 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Other Drafts for Book 3, 1988-1990; 204735 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Other Drafts for Book 4, 1988-1990; 204736 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Other Drafts for Book 5, 1988-1990; 204737 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - "Vollbild AIDS", December 1988-February 1990; 204738 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence with Artists, [1989]; 204739 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Letters to the Editor - "AIDS and Democracy: A Case Study", 1989; 204740 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - "Democracy" (Essays - Rainer, Wallace, and Gates), 1989; 204741 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - "Unisex" for "The Center Show", March 1989; 204742 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - "Shopping Bag", October-November 1989; 204743 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - "Shopping Bag" - Shopping Bags, 1989; 207192 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Corcoran Non-Project, 1989; 204745 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - Berkeley - A+Text-Versions/Notes, 1989; 204746 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - Berkeley (Correspondence, checklists, show, process), 1989; 204747 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - Berkeley - (Announcements, Printed Matter), 1989; 204748 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - Berkeley - Democracy Wall, 1989; 204749 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - Berkeley (Photos of Individual Objects), 1989; 204750 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - Berkeley (Statistics in the show) - 1 of 2, 1989; 204751 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - Berkeley (Statistics in the show) - 2 of 2, 1989; 204752 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Democracy Book - Intros - CP with table and reprint/132 (1 of 2), 1990; 204753 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Democracy Book - P + E - AIDS with Bibliographic resources and Artist List (2 of 2), 1990; 204754 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Democracy (Notes: Organization of Book and Process), 1990; 204755 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Democracy and Cultural Participation Book Draft - 1 of 2, February 2, 1990; 204756 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Democracy and Cultural Participation Book Draft - 2 of 2, February 2, 1990; 204757 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Considered Essays (Not in Final Book), 1990; 204758 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - "Your Message Here" - Proposals for Doug Ashford - Binder, 1990; 204759 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - "Your Message Here", 1990; 204760 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - "Democracy Poll", June-July 1990; 204761 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - "Democracy Poll" (Texts and Research), 1990; 204762 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - "Democracy Poll" (Actual Piece; PR), June-July 1990; 204763 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - "AIDS and Insurance" - Bus Poster/Brochure, 1990; 204764 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Balcon Pages Prop. (unrealized), 1990; 204765 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - "AIDS Timeline" Binder, [1990]; 204766 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - "AIDS Timeline" Magazine project, 1990; 204771 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - "AIDS Timeline" (Sao Paolo Proposal) - unrealized, 1990; 204770 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - "Collaboration" for Oberlin, October 1990 - January 1991; 204772 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - "AIDS Timeline" (Whitney Museum), April-June 1991; 204873 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - "AIDS Timeline" (Whitney) - Text Versions, 1991; 204874 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - [Source Material] - 1 of 10, 1991; 204875 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - [Source Material] - 2 of 10, 1991; 204876 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - [Source Material] - 3 of 10, 1991; 204877 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - [Source Material] - 4 of 10, 1991; 204878 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - [Source Material] - 5 of 10, 1991; 204879 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - [Source Material] - 6 of 10, 1991; 204880 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - [Source Material] - 7 of 10, 1991; 204881 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - [Source Material] - 8 of 10, 1991; 204882 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - [Source Material] - 9 of 10, 1991; 204883 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - [Source Material] - 10 of 10, 1991; 210630 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Art Journal Contribution, Fall 1991; 204884 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Materials] - Mounted Copy of Shift Magazine, [1991]; 210631 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Materials] - 1 of 2, [1991]; 204885 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Materials] - 2 of 2, [1991]; 204886 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Materials] - Magazines - 1 of 2, [1991]; 204887 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Materials] - Magazines - 2 of 2, [1991]; 204888 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Materials] - Photographs, [1991]; 210659 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Materials] - Pray for RU486 bumper sticker, [1991]; 210660 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Materials] - McCarty bumper stickers, [1991]; 210661 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - [Source Material] - Clippings, [1991]; 210662 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - [Source Material] - Public Service Announcements, [1991]; 210663 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - "Cash Prize" [Source Material] - 1 of 2, 1991; 204890 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - "Cash Prize" [Source Material] - 2 of 2, 1991; 204891 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - "Cash Prize" (Correspondence, Process, Admin), December 1991; 204892 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - "Cash Prize" (Research Material and Potential Sources), December 1991; 204889 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - "Cash Prize" (Layouts, Pieces, PR), December 1991; 204893 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - "Family Photo" - Mounted Dynasty photograph for Randolph Street Gallery, 1992; 204894 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - "Tomorrow", 1993; 204895 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - "Democracy Wall" for Boston, October 1993; 204896 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - "Public Interventions" at ICA, 1994; 204897 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - "Campaign" (For Domini Public), 1994; 204898 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - "Market", May-June 1995; 204899 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - "Market" - [Mass Produced Source Material] - 1 of 3, May-June 1995; 204900 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - "Market" - [Mass Produced Source Material] - 2 of 3, May-June 1995; 204901 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - "Market" - [Mass Produced Source Material] - 3 of 3, May-June 1995; 204902 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - "Market" - Advertisements [Source Material], [1995]; 204903 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - "Transaction" for "Architectures of Display", 1995; 204904 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - "Brochure" (Correspondence, Notes, Prop., Aftermath) - Three Rivers Arts Festival - 1 of 2, June 1996; 204905 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - "Brochure" (Correspondence, Notes, Prop., Aftermath) - Three Rivers Arts Festival - 2 of 2, June 1996; 204906 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - "Brochure" (Text Version, Layouts) - Three Rivers Arts Festival, June 1996; 204907 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - "Brochure" (Announcements, Brochure, Festival PR) - Three Rivers Arts Festival, June 1996; 204908 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Unrealized Proposals, undated; 204912 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Subseries C: Catalogs and printed material, 210865
    This series includes material published as part of Group Material projects, press, and source material.
    - "AIDS Timeline" - Magazines published for "Day Without Art" - Afterimage, 1990; 210909 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - Magazines published for "Day Without Art" - Art and Auction, 1990; 210910 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - Magazines published for "Day Without Art" - Art in America, 1990; 210911 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - Magazines published for "Day Without Art" - Arts Magazine, 1990; 210912 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - Magazines published for "Day Without Art" - Contemporanea Number 23, 1990; 210913 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - Magazines published for "Day Without Art" - Copies of Shift Magazine, 1990; 210914 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - Magazines published for "Day Without Art" - High Performance 52, 1990; 210915 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - Magazines published for "Day Without Art" - October 54, 1990; 210916 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - Magazines published for "Day Without Art" - Parkett 26 - 1 of 2, 1990; 210917 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - Magazines published for "Day Without Art" - Parkett 26 - 2 of 2, 1990; 210918 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - Magazines published for "Day Without Art" - Real Life Magazine 20, 1990; 210919 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Archbishop Romero [Source Material], 1980; 211363 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - "The Castle" [Source Material] - book by Franz Kafka, 1981-1982; 211364 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Issues of Upfront - Political Art Documentation/Distribution, 1982-1983; 211365 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Photo Communique - [Source Material], 1984; 211366 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - The Public Art Show, 1985; 211367 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Material] - Surviving and Thriving with AIDS Volume 1, 1987; 211368 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - "Constitution" catalog, 1987; 205982 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - The Science of AIDS [Source Material], 1988; 205983 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Vollbild - Tableaux du Sida, 1988; 211372 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Vollbild - AIDS, 1988; 211373 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - "AIDS Timeline" - [Exhibited Materials] - Surviving and Thriving with AIDS - volume 2, 1988; 211374 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Art Against AIDS - [Source Material], 1989; 211375 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - My Turn - Memoirs of Nancy Reagan [Source Material], 1989; 211376 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Reconnaissance - Catalog with Group Material's " Shopping Cart", 1990; 211377 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Art Journal - Censorship project, 1991; 211378 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - "Pure Cop" - [Source Material], 1991; 211379 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Christian Action Network - Home Lobbyist Companion - [Source Material], 1994; 211380 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Walt Odet's book - In the Shadow of an Epidemic - [Source Material], 1995; 211381 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - "Matrix" -A Changing Exhibition of Contemporary Art, undated; 210629 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Subseries D: Advertisements from "Market", 1995; 210904
    This series includes mounted advertisements, which were originally exhibited in "Market."
    - "Market" - Aurora - Mounted Advertisement, 1995; 208664 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - "Market" - AT&T - Mounted Advertisement, 1995; 208663 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - "Market" - Lockheed Martin - Mounted Advertisement, 1995; 208662 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - "Market" - Kraft - Mounted Advertisement, 1995; 208661 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - "Market" - Desert Storm - Mounted Advertisement, 1995; 208660 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - "Market" - Microsoft - Mounted Advertisement (German) - 1 of 3, 1995; 208659 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - "Market" - Microsoft - Mounted Advertisement (German) - 2 of 3, 1995; 208658 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - "Market" - Microsoft - Mounted Advertisement (German) - 3 of 3, 1995; 208657 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - "Market" - Microsoft Mounted Advertisement (English) - 1 of 2, 1995; 208656 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - "Market" - Microsoft Mounted Advertisement (English) - 2 of 2, 1995; 208655 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - "Market" - McDonnell Douglas Mounted Advertisement, 1995; 208654 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - "Market" - Skirmish - Mounted Advertisement, 1995; 208653 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - "Market" - AT&T - Mounted Advertisement, 1995; 208652 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - "Market" - Donna Karan - Mounted Advertisement - 1 of 4, 1995; 208651 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - "Market" - Donna Karan - Mounted Advertisement - 2 of 4, 1995; 208650 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - "Market" - Donna Karan - Mounted Advertisement - 3 of 4, 1995; 208649 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - "Market" - Donna Karan - Mounted Advertisement - 4 of 4, 1995; 208648 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - "Market" - Surveillance Strike - Mounted Advertisement, 1995; 208665 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - "Market" - Coca Cola, Tall, Dark - Mounted Advertisement, 1995; 208666 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - "Market" - hand with gun - Mounted Advertisement, 1995; 208667 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - "Market" - Coca Cola - Always - Mounted Advertisement, 1995; 208668 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - "Market" - Nike - Michael Jordan - Mounted Advertisement, 1995; 208670 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - "Market" - Saab - Mounted Advertisement, 1995; 208671 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - "Market" - United States Armed Forces - Mounted Advertisement, 1995; 208672 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - "Market" - Ronald Reagan - Mounted Advertisement, 1995; 208673 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - "Market" - American Express - Mounted Advertisement, 1995; 208674 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - "Market" - Cindy Crawford - Mounted Advertisement, 1995; 208675 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - "Market" - Northrop Grumman - Mounted Advertisement, 1995; 208676 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Series II: Correspondence, 204536
  Arranged chronologically, this series includes correspondence by members of Group Material with artists, contractors, and other individuals. The material was compiled by Julie Ault and placed in chronological order by the archivist.
  - General Correspondence with Group Material Letterhead, 1980-1988; 210698 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence from Doug Ashford, 1988-2005; 208389 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - General Correspondence, 1989; 204915 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - General Correspondence, 1990; 204916 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, 1992; 204917 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, 1992-1994; 210664 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, 1995-2007; 204918 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence with Taschen, 1998; 210665 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence - undated, 204919 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Series III: Press and Promotional Material, 204538
  Organized chronologically, this series contains articles, reviews, research for press materials, posters, and other promotional material related to Group Material exhibitions.
  - Subseries A: Interviews, research, reviews, 210862
    - "AIDS Timeline" Magazines - Text, undated; 205211 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Articles, 1980-1986; 205190 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - First Year Press (13th St.) ("The People's Choice," "Atlanta," "Consumption"), 1981; 205191 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Press ("Primer", "Luchar!", "Subculture", etc.), 1981-1983; 205192 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Press ("Timeline", "Democracy Wall", "Americana", "Messages to Washington"), 1984-1986; 205193 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - "Press" ("MASS," One Foot out the Door, "Constitution," "Castle," "Resistance," etc.), 1986-1987; 205194 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Articles, Interviews, Statements, 1987-1990; 205195 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Press ("Inserts", "Democracy", "AIDS Timeline"), 1988-1989; 205198 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Articles, 1988-1990; 205197 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Group Material Lecture Announcements and Related, 1988-1991; 205196 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Interview Transcripts 1, [1989]; 205199 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Interview Transcripts 2, [1989-1991]; 205200 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Signs and Postcards and Civil Disobedience Flowchart, 1989; 205206 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Press ("Democracy Poll", VMH, "Collaboration", "AIDS and Insurance"), 1990; 205201 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Magazine - Visual Aids, [1990]; 205202 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Press - "AIDS Timeline" Hartford, [AT NY], "Cash Prize," Democracy Book - 1 of 2, 1990-1991; 204767 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Press - "AIDS Timeline" Hartford, [AT NY], "Cash Prize," Democracy Book - 2 of 2, 1990-1991; 204768 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - General, 1990-1997; 205207 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - "Rhetorical Image" Resource Form, 1991; 205209 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, Notes, Press, Whitney "AIDS Timeline", [1991]; 205208 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous group shows Group Material was in, [1991-1993]; 205203 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Press (In and Out of Place, "Tomorrow", "Public Intervention", "Campaign", "Market"), 1993-1995; 205204 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Press (But is it Art?, Brochure...), 1996; 205205 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Articles, undated; 205213 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Doug Ashford Interviews and Lectures, undated; 205212 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Binder Five - Press materials, undated; 206845 (Box 19)
  - Subseries B: Magazines, 211353
    - Real Life Magazine, 1983; 211389 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Contemporary Perspectives, 1984; 211390 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - "Anti-Baudrillard" - File Megazine 28, 1987; 211391 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Wolkenkratzer, 1987; 211392 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Art Papers 12/5, 1988; 211393 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Artscribe, 1989; 211394 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Parachute 56, 1989; 211395 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Art Papers 14/1, 1990; 211396 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Prinz, 1990; 211397 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Wadsworth Atheneum, 1990; 211398 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Shift 9, 1990; 211399 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Social Studies, 1990-1991; 211400 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - BT Magazine 43, 1991; 211401 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - "In Public Seattle 1991", 211402 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Tema Celeste, 1991; 211403 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Utne Reader, 1991; 211404 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - La Vanguardia, 1994; 211405 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Series IV: Clippings, undated; 204539
  Kept in its original order, this series is comprised of clippings, articles, advertisements, and mass-produced items such as bumper stickers collected for research and potential inclusion in exhibitions, saved by Julie Ault, with Group Material in mind.
  - Clippings 1, undated; 205214 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Clippings 2, undated; 205215 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Clippings 3, undated; 205216 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Clippings 4, undated; 205217 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Clippings 5, undated; 205218 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Clippings 6, undated; 205219 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Clippings 7, undated; 205220 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Clippings 8, undated; 205221 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Clippings 9, undated; 205222 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Clippings 10, undated; 205223 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Clippings 11, undated; 205224 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Clippings 12, undated; 205225 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Clippings 13, undated; 205226 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Clippings 14, undated; 205227 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Clippings 15, undated; 205228 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Clippings 16, undated; 205229 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Series V: Financial Material, 1977-1944; 204537
  Arranged chronologically, this series includes checks, receipts, bills and other financial files collected by Group Material members.
  - Bank Statements and Deposit Slips, 1977-1986; 205232 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Group Material - Legal Papers, 1980-1987; 205233 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Group Material - Receipts and Bills, 1980-1981; 205234 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Con Edison Bills, 1981; 205235 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - National Endowment for the Arts - 1981-1987 Applications and Correspondence, 205236 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Bills - Kreisel Company, 1981; 205237 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Receipts 1983, c. 1983; 205238 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Group Material Receipts, c. 1984; 205239 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - General Journal, 1984-1985; 205240 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - "Group Material Inc." - Binder - 1 of 2, 1985; 205242 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - "Group Material Inc." - Binder - 2 of 2, 1985; 205243 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Receipts 1985, c. 1985; 205241 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Group Material Check Stubs, 1986-1988; 205244 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Receipts 1986, c. 1986; 205245 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Receipts: Documenta, Anti-Baudrillard, Travel, 1986-1988; 205246 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Group Material Check Stubs, 1986-1989; 205247 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Group Material Receipts, 1987-1988; 205248 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Art Matters, 1987-1990; 205249 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Receipts - Doug Ashford, Julie Ault, 1989-1991; 205250 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - National Endowment for the Arts 1989-1991 Application 1 of 2, 205251 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - National Endowment for the Arts 1989-1991 Application 2 of 2, 205252 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Group Material Receipts 1990, 205253 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Tax Exempt Forms, 1990; 205254 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Receipts, 1993-1997; 205255 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Check Stubs, 1994; 205256 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Amalgamated Bank Statements, undated; 205257 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - New York State Council on the Arts (NYSCA), undated; 205258 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Forms and Guidelines, undated; 205259 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Checks, undated; 205260 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - National Endowment for the Arts (Interim and Final Reports), undated; 205261 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Series VI: Photographic Material, 204542
  Images in this series document various aspects of each exhibition, including photographs of installations, opening receptions, and artworks. The series is comprised of photographic prints, black and white and color negatives, slides, and 35mm film. Additional photographic material from Group Material projects is found in series I. This series also includes images selected from the larger pool of photography for the book Show and Tell: A Chronicle of Group Material.
  - Inaugural Show Photos, 1980; 206345 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - "Salon of Election" Photos, 1980; 206347 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - "No More Witch Hunts" Photos, 1980; 206348 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - General Photos and Snapshots [From Mundy McLaughlin], [1980-1990]; 206772 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - "The People's Choice" Photos, 1981; 206349 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - General Slides, 1981-1989; 206773 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - General Exhibition Slides, 1981-1989; 206774 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Slides and Negatives - "4 x 5's", 1981-1986; 206775 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - "Primer (For Raymond Williams)" photos, 1982; 206350 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - General Slides, 1982-1990; 206776 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Slides, 1982-1996; 206777 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Slides - Doug Ashford [copies of duplicate slides], 1982-1996; 206780 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - "Subculture" Photos, 1983; 206361 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - "Timeline: The Chronicle of U.S Intervention in Latin and Central America" at PS1 Photos, 1984; 206362 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - "Timeline: The Chronicle of U.S Intervention in Latin and Central America" in "1984 Show" at PS1, 206363 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - "Democracy Wall" For Cardiff Photos, 1985; 206394 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - "Americana" Photos, 1985; 206395 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - "MASS" photos, 1985; 206396 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - "Constitution", 1987; 206397 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - "The Castle", 1987; 206398 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - "Resistance (Anti-Baudrillard)", 1987; 206399 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - "Democracy: Education", 1988; 206400 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - "Democracy", 1988-1989; 206407 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Photographs - "AIDS Timeline", 1988-1989; 206408 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - "Democracy: Cultural Participation", 1988-1989; 206409 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - "Democracy: AIDS and Democracy: A Case Study", 1988-1989; 206410 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Group Material - Photo Album - Julie Ault, 1988-1994; 206412 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Individual Artists + Research - prints and slides, 1988-1996; 206791 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Inserts, 1988; 206411 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - "Shopping Bag", 1989; 206413 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Vollbild AIDS Photos, 1989; 206414 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - "AIDS Timeline" Photos, 1989-1991; 206415 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - "AIDS Timeline" Magazine Photos, 1990; 206416 (Box 10, Folder 14)